Jhal Hello friends, once again a
very welcome to your own YouTube
channel, its name is Share Market and you have
seen it many times, so friends, in this video we are going to talk about
Trips To Perform His
Stocks, the IPO of 2021 came
in 2021 and they had a tremendous performance
and even today they perform tremendously,
you can see that, so friends, now we will talk about
those stocks on three bases of 2021, yes, those
whose IPL came in 2021 and had a
tremendous impact and share, they
were IPOs of branded companies and
even after being branded, a tremendous decline has been
seen in them and friends, let's start and
see which Trips To Perform His Stocks have
reached in 2021 and which are the Triple
Performance Stocks after the IPO of 2021, so
friends, let's start
and talk about the first one, but
before moving forward, friends, if you have
not subscribed to our channel yet, then
please do subscribe to the channel and press the
bell icon so that the video upload
notifications start giving you timely feedback.  Let's do it
and the stock which has been taken at number one is
named Easy 111. Yes, if we
talk about iPad, then from March 8, friend,
kill it friend, whose IPO
price was done between 197 pieces and if we talk about
listing, it happened on 19 March 2021
and this listing price band was 212
at a premium of 13% at that time and the current
price of Singh is ₹500 and if we
look at the percentage corn return, till now it has
given a return of 300% when it
dried up, where it has seen a
great return of 300% from active consumption till now.
Friends, let's move ahead and talk about the
second number, which is Clean Science
and Technology's IPO which came
between July 2021 and the price of the IPO was
on the auspicious occasion and it was listed on
19 July 2021 and the listing
price was Rs 1784
at a premium of 98% and the issue price is your current
price  It is Rs 2585. If we
talk about returns in percentage, then there are
tremendous returns.
You have also got a great return of 2087 percent since its IPO came.
Friends, if we talk about this, then
Sona is also known as Develop Receiver
and
its IPO came fourth which is going to Indore from June 16 to
June 24, and between which is it
because its share was listed at Rs.21 on
June 24, 2021 and its
listing price was ₹10 from there, which was at a
four percent premium to this price
and if we talk about the current price, then the
current price is more than and till now
it has seen great returns. When I drank tea, it is
around 250 three percent. Friends, I
heard that BMW is a great stock, very great.
Friends, let's move ahead and talk.
Now, after the IPO on Free Bed, it has
given the best performance in 2021, so at
number one is your Surya. If we talk about this small
finance bank and Village Taipei,
then 17  It was most loved between 19 March 2019
and till then you had all the shares at ₹5.
It was listed
in the market on 26 March 2001 and if we talk about the
listing price, then it had a break of ₹2,
which was four and a half percent of the
last over. Its issue price for
current price is around ₹45
and its percentage loss is about
22% loss. It has seen investors
since its IPO came in the market. Let's move ahead
and talk about the
second number stock. Its second number
stock is in front of you. Its heart rate was when
its IPO came on 9 August, so it will
definitely be in between and the
IPO price was ₹1618 per share.
It came in the market on 20 August
2002 and if we talk about the listing
price, then its listing price was ₹16100
and its current
price now  It is something like 822 and the
percentage loss it has given till now is a
loss of about 59%. This is an investor question.
Since its IPO came in the market,
Prince moves ahead. Now let's talk about the
third one. It is known as ATM Yoni
's 197 Communications. If
you want, it was between November 8 and 10,
2021. The IPO proposal was for
one share at ₹50. And if we talk about
its listing date, it was listed on November 18, 2021.
And if we talk about its
listing price, then its listing
price was ₹1950, that is, by this measure, send billota on your husband
and the current price is ₹1232.
And till now it has given approximately
14%
losses to the investors. Yes,
it has seen a huge loss. Paytm. So friends, in this way
you saw that after the IPO of three strong performers
and three bad stocks,
which  If you are looking for it, then friends, an
attempt has been made to give a message that whenever you
go for parties, keep Akshay Bhare
Bhartiya on it and definitely study it
and find out the material, what is its work,
how is it, is it not too expensive,
definitely make such small marks
and friends, stay with us,
definitely subscribe to our channel,
thank you very much for watching the video.